It's been a while
CEO Jaebeom Yoo
Yes, it's been a while.
CEO Oh
Ah, that
Thank you very much
Now, Detective Woo.
There are a lot of shells on the hemp cloth.
This house is fundamental, huh?
Now
Whoo, whoo, whoo~
Now, do one thing.
Right here!
That's what happened to me here
Ah, it happened that someone like the judge
You've been scammed
If you approach me as a friend from my hometown,
You borrowed money and ran away?
Ha, really…
i go to this store
I didn't want to come back again
So
Jaebeom Yoo Where is that bastard now?
Ha, I was hiding in Cambodia.
With a fake passport 1 year ago
It was confirmed that you entered the country.
His whereabouts after that are unknown.
Yeah?
And then he got close to me
No, even my first love as a child
I knew everything
Where on earth did they do their background research on me?
fact
I asked Judge Kang
I have something to ask you.
To me? What is it?
Ah, Jaebeom Yoo
At Incheon Airport upon arrival
Opened in the name of a fake passport
I have a prepaid phone.
I checked the call history.
- But?
- Ah, but
Especially the number that was dialed multiple times.
I have it…
- This number...
- Yes
Seocho-dong, Seocho-gu, Seoul
Seoul Central District Court Criminal Agreement Department
Chief Judge David Kang's office
Is this the judge's room phone number?
What are you talking about!
Why am I talking to that bastard?
I never once
I got on the phone with that person...
An elementary school classmate
You called
‘Kim Joo-seop’?
Who is it?
If you say it's a jujeop, you'll know it...
Jujeop…
Oh, that Kim Joo-jeop?
why?
Is there anything you want to point out?
good morning!
Judge, you agreed to the personnel verification, right?
no way…
Star!
Ah, star!
Thank you so much, lawyer.
Thank you so much
Lawyers, really.
Star!
Never again
I thought I wouldn't be able to see it
Ha, thank you
But
Is it really going to end like this?
What should I do if they harass me again while I appeal?
don't worry
You can't appeal.
Just trust me
I will protect you
Let's go
Attorney Park
Why is your face so red?
- yes?
- Well, do you have a fever?
- uh! kid
- Fish oil, why...
No, it's okay.
I don't have a fever, I'm fine.
Well, well, well…
what? this person…
What is this reaction?
Uh, okay, well, if that's okay, that's fine.
Well…
Let's go
Ah, over there
Why can’t I appeal?
Because they changed their words first...
The moon worked hard too
Ha, that doesn't work.
Ha, here we go again, my heart
my heart is beating
Wingardium Leviosa!
Lumos!
yes
Wingardium Leviosa!
The first court I ever went to was
It was a scary place
Wingardium leviosa
order
Huh!
Uh, mom, mom, mom
The order the judge memorized at that moment was
Appearing in ‘Harry Potter’
More than all those orders
It was an even cooler magic spell.
'The child's guardian is
‘Children at home’
'According to his growth period'
'Healthy and safe'
'Must be nurtured'
Ah, in Article 99 of the Civil Act
Definition of movable property and real estate
It's coming out
Well, then here
Howl's Moving Castle
Is it chattel? Is it real estate?
ah…
moving? Howl…
and the second
Student Park Gi-ppeum
Uh, yes, professor.
Oh, you did well in the interview?
Ah, thank you
Now that the interview is over
Shall we talk in peace?
yes
Why do you want to become a lawyer?
This too is now a declining industry.
Yes, as I said earlier.
I defend basic human rights
Social...
Hey, the interview is over.
Other than that, the real reason
really
That's why?
Okay
But
Virtue and reality were different.
The thing that makes my heart pound
It hasn't been for a very long time since then.
I did that
Cruelly abused and abandoned
This poor abandoned dog
really lost witness
Is that the dog?
No, no, no
I was excited, but then
Just for a moment
Wow
That's it
Just trust me, kid.
What are you worried about?
Is there this national judge, David Kang?
Ah, of course
Attorney Kang’s skills are great.
It's enormous.
I respect you, really.
But what's the problem?
But no matter what
This trillion-dollar international patent case...
Also, disputes between large corporations
What we do
Well, how far can we go
Because we are a team dedicated to public interest litigation.
Wow, it’s frustrating, really.
Wow
What is public interest?
No, we're a team now
Let’s just say it out loud
Let's talk, okay?
If we win and make a lot of money
Where does all that money go? yes?
Because money is spinning around
Common people and the weak
Everyone benefits.
I'm making money
It's the best public interest.
Hey, it's like day and night, huh?
Something like this
It's not even worth the money, huh?
Just holding my arms up and losing strength
Why do you do things like this?
yes? What is it?
Refugee case?
no, now
Young people are in trouble because they don't have jobs.
Who is a foreigner coming in?
Are you happy, yes?
What else? Human rights for the disabled?
Words are beautiful, aren't they?
Whenever disabled people protest
Office workers who can't commute to work properly
Do you know how much it hurts?
Hey, let’s not do things like this, okay?
Form, I have a case...
iced coffee!
Let’s listen, let’s listen, really!
Now in public interest litigation
Denying the value of existence itself
Do I have to listen to this?
What, everyone has nothing to say?
- ah…
- now
Am I the only one who feels uncomfortable?
- ah…
-No~
What's wrong with Yu Byun?
Are you uncomfortable with everything? yes?
Oh, if it's uncomfortable
Go sit in a comfortable place.
Ha…
What a brat!
what?
A brat?
Oh, I'm really clueless, am I?
What, old man?
Ugh, I sound like an old brat.
Is this your first time hearing this?
Hey, Yu Byun.
Yes? What did you say just now, old man?
What!
In my time, yes?
You couldn't even step on your senior's shadow, old boy?
I guess my heart is acting like a fan
Man, the legal profession has really gotten better.
this time
I guess it rang wrong
- After all, physiognomy is a science...
- Use earphones when talking.
-Why are you wearing it? Really now...
- Oh, I fought from the beginning.
Ha, look at this, Attorney Kang.
speech
What grade are you in now?
- yes?
- Attorney Kang
U, ah…
Ha, why Park Byun again?
Attorney Kang
Why did you come to Pro Bono?
Why is that so suddenly...
As you said
A person who only did fashionable cases
Why did you even quit being a judge?
Did you come here?
Do you know Attorney Kang?
In the world
As there are always people who win
People who live by always losing
That there is
No matter how hard you try
Fighting with the world
people who struggle
to help those people
There is covariance
A case that always wins
To do a stylish event
No
Why do you think I don't know?
People who always lose
No matter how hard you try
Fighting with the world
people who struggle
You think I don’t know?
Do you know Park Byun?
Are you in that situation?
Well, yourself
Have you earned any tuition?
Lawyer Kang
You speak too much
Right? These questions are uncomfortable, right?
I think it would have been unpleasant
Sorry, Excuse Me
no
Thanks to my parents
In a home without any shortages
I was loved and raised
Yes, it looks just like that
But why is that?
Is there any problem?
No, who cares?
It's so great
Wow, this is really great.
The one who grew up loved and cherished
Are you worried about the common people and the weak?
Oh, that's so great, Byun Park.
Do you want to try politics?
let me help you
Do you know a lot of people?
Oh, really!
Attorney Park
Follow me, follow me
If you have a sister, you should come see her.
We want to get married too
we have a little
very little
It's just different
please understand us
Lawyers are with you
We are together
Please give me a hug!
sexual minority human rights
Lawyers are with you!
Sign and go!
- Please, sign.
- Please
Let’s create a world without discrimination together!
Make it, sign it.
If you donate and participate in surveys,
We'll give you a t-shirt!
sexual minority human rights
Lawyers are with you
Get a t-shirt!
free t-shirt, signed
Wow, the lawyer
What are you sitting doing?
One of the main tasks of Gongbyeon is
This is a support activity for human rights organizations.
We are together
Get a t-shirt!
IC
- I can't do it.
- No way, right?
- No, no, this.
- Come to the festival and do this
I paid a lot of money to be a lawyer
I'm not going to sit down
- That's right.
- Okay, let's go, let's go.
-Why?
- Please give me a hug!
what?
Follow me!
evil!
Ouch! Mr.
Ah, why…
Nanhee
- Come out, come out, come out.
- Ooh, ooh, ooh!
I'm a celebrity
What if someone finds out...
If you came to the festival
You must dress appropriately for TPO!
You're talking like TPO
Well, it's like this, well
Are people coming?
Me, together
Can you take a picture?
Yes, just one.
- Are you coming?
- thank you!
Now, one, two, three
It's pretty, really!
You are so beautiful
Ah, ah, ah, no, I…
Ah, I am a man among men…
Why is your tone like this?
I will support you, fighting!
- Fighting
- The person who took the photo
Come this way
I would like to ask you to sign my name.
Ah, yes
Please sign
Get a t-shirt too
Yu Byun, give me my pants.
-Where are your pants?
- Us too
Please take just one photo!
- oh! Shall we take a picture?
-Take a picture!
- Yes, I like it!
- Are you pretty?
I'll take a picture, one, two, three.
- Yes, thank you, Yu Byun, stop.
- One, two, three
- Cool!
- Yubyeon
- Smile!
- Slightly
Please take a few more pictures
Oh my~
one, two, three
Byun Yu, that’s it, yes, thank you.
That's enough, that's done, that's done
Yu Byun, it’s okay…
and! Please take a picture with me, please, wow!
I love it so much
Now, let's take a picture together.
Now
Me too, me too!
- Okay, let's take a picture.
- Take a few pictures.
I'll take a picture
Let’s all smile together!
Huh, look at this, Byun Park.
Like this all day
Are you going to drag me somewhere?
Are you doing this on purpose?
Oh my, what are you saying?
This is the daily life of public defenders.
If you have any questions about legal issues
we have to answer
Of course
I have a question
If there is
ha
- I'm sorry.
-Sigh~
Really hard this time
I prepared a press release.
It's okay
Lawyer Kang
- Ah...
- Oh my, oh my
Wow
- Ah...
-Are you okay?
It's okay
Did you have a good time?
No, why, why, why, why, why...
What's wrong?
Wait a minute
Let's go
No, why, why, why, why, why...
- What's wrong?
- Hello
hello
How have you been?
- How have you been?
- Attorney Jang
I guess they brought in another reporter I know.
He said that last time too
Hmm
- Hello
- Mushroom stone has surprisingly wide feet?
- Fighting
- With the people here.
I feel like I know everything
Attorney Jang
He's a legend in this version.
- Huh?
- When I was a college student
At the illegal demolition site of the shantytown.
I fought with some hired thugs.
So much so that the gangsters are scared
They say it was bloody
- Jang Byeon?
- Yes
Oh no, what nonsense...
But that suit
It's old, but it's definitely
Seen at a select shop in Cheongdam-dong
Is it similar to an Italian luxury product?
Is it fake?
I
Can I ask you a question?
Yes, you do.
yes
yes, nice to meet you
‘One step taken together’
This is reporter Go Il-ju.
Hi go
- Recurring foreign workers…
- At least one person came.
labor movement reporter
It's the vegetables and the rice.
Uh, Jeongin.
I was trying to call you
You really
They told me to cooperate.
Am I really like this?
Come in?
Park Byun, he wants to come in, quickly.
Now, now, hey, hey
Now, hey! Hehehe
Where are you going!
“O&Partners”
This abandoned dog incident
public participation trial
To citizens
It's becoming a big topic.
Ah, the best large law firm in the country.
O&Partners
Free defense of this case
The fact that I was in charge
It's attracting attention again
When it comes to O&Partners, honestly.
Ordinary people don't even dare to dream
There is an image that the threshold is high, right?
ah…
Yes, I had that image.
I admit it
But now the world has changed, right?
We must change too
Social responsibility, changing times
Oh my, if you miss something like this
It's not fun, yeah
The newly born O&Partners
Please look forward to it
Well, the young female lawyer
Becoming a representative lawyer
Just by itself
Isn't it an amazing change?
My age and gender are news stories
A world that doesn't work
I'm going to try making that.
Ah, yes
Oh, you're great.
Oh, and famous as a national judge.
Attorney David Kang
You were in charge of this case.
I heard you two were classmates at the training center?
How did you recruit him?
Could you tell us a little bit?
Ah
That's directly
Let’s ask Attorney Kang.
Shall we stop for a moment?
Fish oil~
You work hard, oh lawyer
Are you good at interviews too?
As expected, the national judge force
It's still the same
There's one thing I'm curious about
What is it?
Why don't you ask a single question?
what?
The incident that made me quit being a judge
You never asked?
Have you seen the video?
I
Do you need to know?
what?
I still can't come to my senses
the person who works here
Do you know how many people there are?
There are over 1,000 lawyers alone.
Secretary to Paralegal Girl
As for other employees
How much?
How many of them are former Supreme Court Justices?
Prosecutor General, Minister, Commissioner of National Tax Service
Do you know how many bank presidents there are?
Even the democracy fighter politicians who attacked us
Journalists called the conscience of the times
Receive a torture business card
While receiving a rough salary
I'm working hard
O&Partners
It's Korea itself
know?
Ah
Sorry, brother
I take care of every detail of my employees.
I'm not free enough to take care of it.
Then
hard work
Oh, are you here, lawyer?
- Yes, what about the other team members?
- I went out to work.
I enjoyed the news yesterday
You're really cool
- Thank you
- Well, but, that
I saw the interview yesterday
There is someone who came to visit me.
Recklessly
Please let me meet Attorney Kang...
huh?
Who are you suing?
God
I told you just now
Do you go to church? Or a cathedral?
no
Who in the world can you trust?
I don't trust anyone
Ah, but why?
I want to receive compensation for my damages
very much
Compensation for damages?
So you're a civil servant, not a detective?
yes
What did God do wrong to you?
You made me born
Huh?
I never wanted it
Being born into the world like this
no one ever wanted
I was born
Mom too
Even the father I’ve never seen
So please do it
free defense
Ha…
You said you would do it?
I?
I've been involved all my life
What left the court
in a lower place
for those who suffer
To stand by your side
There is no way to get help in the future
When the weak come to me
I've built up all my life
With legal knowledge and experience
Let us help you
Ah, this
Because you are still young
I don't know
When a trial makes sense
You can only bet if there is a chance of winning.
Making it make sense
Isn’t that what lawyers do?
Are you a lawyer?
Why are you holding your horse’s tail like this?
It's okay, please do it
trial for damages
Ha…
So what?
What, your treatment costs are a loss?
What, tell God to compensate?
There's no cure anyway
Before
congenital paralysis of the lower extremities
Okay, then what loss...
I told you
I was born
I'm in this world
Being alive itself is a loss.
I would rather
It was so much better not to have been born.
Did you send it?
I barely sent it
Wow, how stubborn that kid is.
No, they say they live in Bucheon.
I don't know how I got there
Bucheon? But did you send it alone?
Take a large taxi
Sent
I used my own money again
I gave the driver plenty of taxi fare.
Okay, good job.
- Hey...
- why?
Well, Attorney Kang
It's like a visitor.
What about guests...
so?
I paid enough for taxi fare with my own money…
The destination is Bucheon, ah, this…
Okay, good job.
yes
Do you have anything to say?
no
Let's go, let's have a drink of soju
Yes?
yes!
under…
I told you
I was born
I'm in this world
Being alive itself is a loss.
Oh, little guy
They say all sorts of things.
Are you feeling a little off?
Ha, this is a public defense case.
This is so...
Well, it's Attorney Kang.
Well, this is probably your first time experiencing something like this.
-More...
- Ha, what was the first...
yes?
When I was first hired, the support was small.
I've done everything
When serving as judge
Personal rehabilitation, personal bankruptcy
I had a concurrent job
Wow, I couldn't eat it.
Because there are too many incidents?
Well, that's it too
Every day, my house gets ruined.
Get sick and commit suicide
Because I look at those things every day
It was a bit like that
Let's put out the emergency fire first.
It's obvious that it will keep repeating itself
That's right
So if I could
These people are rich and powerful
I want to do a case
That sounds weird again
I think I'll feel at ease
That, that…
Make more money
Wow
Fish oil, hey
I will eat it gratefully.
No, Mac, have a beer, ah…
You sound like beer
Ah…
Hey, taxi fare
My child, my house, even my house
Is 20,000 won enough?
Uh, bring the change tomorrow.
Thank you, brother!
Come in!
See you tomorrow!
Hey, is he tired?
uh?
Hey, hey, how's it going?
I caught up with you on my way home from work.
Are you coming to Sejin University Hospital?
special room
Uh, it's coming out now.
Oh, I guess my grandmother went to the hospital.
Did I need more hospital bills?
Shall we follow further?
Uh, please keep track of my movements for the time being.
Find out the identities of people you meet
There must be someone else
Ha, judge.
Send me to bread to help me come to my senses.
He even found me a job later.
I’m really grateful for the grace.
Ha, this is
Aren’t you pampering yourself too much?
Will you pay enough for my trouble?
You're fussing, stop it.
Oh my...
taxi!
hello
Sadang-dong
Man, the shrine…
ah…
Sadang Station Exit 2
Start driving
for your safety
Please wear your seat belt
When you get off
Have you left anything behind?
Please check
I…
Go, mop, wet, ni, da
I said no
I said I would do it for you.
- When me?
- Show me again?
A broadcast is a broadcast
The judge appeared on the broadcast
Can I lie?
When did I lie?
And I'm not a judge?
Are you a lawyer?
Then, I want to go to the broadcasting station too.
The lawyer appeared on TV
Is it okay to lie or not?
- Ask me.
- Are you a lawyer?
Why do you keep doing this?
Hold your tongue? Come to work
- What?
- fast
Come to work, come home...
Who's the kid and who's the lawyer?
- That guy is a lawyer.
- Hey
Ouch!
Good morning, uncle.
Not good morning
Huh?
yes, there is
Yes, there are people.
I know~
Hey, you…
It's here~
Sweets in our office
I brought it all
Is this the most delicious?
yes
Uh...
- uh?
- How did you get here?
- Kim Kang-hoon
- Huh? Kang Hoon's mother
What are you doing here?
- Ugh!
- Uh, uh, uh, uh!
Mother, why, why, why, why, why, why...
you really
Do you want to see your mom die? uh!
How long have I been looking for you!
- You really can’t stay home!
- uh…
Mother, sit down calmly.
- Let’s talk…
- Get out of the way!
- Hey, hey, hey...
- uh!
Let go
Let go of this!
I will report this as child abuse.
I'll call the police
Ugh, let go!
Let go!
Don't do it
Well, at least I have nowhere to go.
Don't do that, it's useless...
It's not always the same as before
I take medication for depression.
I guess I can't control it well
Yes, sir, I
- It's like that sometimes.
- Now
- I found the kid...
- I guess
It's good for moms to get help from experts...
I don't like shelters.
never
Kang Hoon, to your mom…
Mom is
He was abandoned by his parents when he was nine years old.
I hate orphanages so much
After running away
kids who left home
I lived in a place where people gathered together.
They say I came into existence when I was sixteen.
Kang Hoon-a
If there really is such a thing as God
I really want to ask you something
What on earth are you thinking?
Why bother?
Why am I like this...
Kang Hoon-a
I have to go now
Take care, mother.
Let's do it, sue?
yes
I thought this was going to be a trial
Are you saying that?
Even if I don't win
Maybe someone will be interested
What is a trial
Is this a public broadcast to help needy neighbors?
This could be a meaningful lawsuit.
through trial
underprivileged and disabled people
Problems about life...
You're saying you're full
Lawyer Kang
Why?
Did I say something uncomfortable again?
Then not me
Well, let’s ask Jang Byun.
Jang Byun, what do you think?
Oh my, keep going
Don’t just pick some mushrooms!
Uh, kinda
- It's difficult.
- Um
Standing in court
Isn't this a normal thing?
To Kang Hoon
It might just hurt you...
Me too
My opinion is that it will be a bit difficult.
This is a lawsuit that is sure to be dismissed.
Well, first of all
Well, if the defendant is God...
Where should I send the delivery address?
I'm not sure
- Child...
- what?
Well, I can do it somehow
To make legal sense
Let's configure it.
And then…
Hope Advisor
how painful it is
Do you even know?
Ugh
- Because I’m a brat anyway.
- Wow, I'm surprised.
Let me say one more thing.
Now Attorney Park
Things being said
That's all typical
This is the idea of flowers in a greenhouse.
Lawyer Kang
In a home without any shortages
You said you grew up loved, right?
What about those people?
I don't know what real hardship is.
Do you pose a problem to society?
What does it mean even if you don’t win?
That's it for that kid
How does it help?
But
Public interest litigation...
Attorney Park too
You came into this firm to make money!
Because I got good grades
The person who joined Korea’s No. 1 law firm
What kind of change of heart came later?
I don't want to know and I don't know
This story is so unrealistic
I wish I didn't
Do you want to do good things?
Donate, you better.
Do the calculation here too.
fish oil, fish oil, fish oil
Ah, Attorney Kang…
What does it mean even if you don’t win?
That's it for that kid
How does it help?
Ha, is that so?
risk of social criticism
Because it always exists
legal response plan
Must be promoted in parallel
That's it.
Hey, Attorney Park Gippeum is also excellent.
Pros and cons of each plan, comparative analysis
Very neat job
thank you
Okay then
Everyone should go to number 3, right?
- Yes
- Lawyer!
As for plan 3, as I wrote in the report…
'Labor Standards Act
'By circumventing the law'
'Employees of target companies
'It is a plan to cause mass layoffs'
- That's right, I saw it well.
- Yes
Oh, so it's not in there.
Let’s do plan 1…
Are you saying this is evading the law?
Then it's not outright illegal.
Then there is less judicial risk.
In addition, labor costs
Significantly reduce it?
This, this
There's no reason not to, right?
yes
no
But…
Attorney Park
Byun Park is now making that naive sound
Aren’t you old enough to stop?
Please don't think about useless things.
focus on the numbers
Sales, Cost, Profit
Okay?
Isn't it?
- Yes, that's right.
- Yes
hello
No, there
Lawyer Gippeum Park, yes?
Our team is here
How hard is it to get in?
Quit this and what?
A team dedicated to public interest?
Are you going there?
Because I like that job.
Hey, don't do that.
Shall we talk about the real reason?
By any chance, what
Is it because you have thoughts about politics?
Well, to build a career.
no
I really want to do that
Yes, lawyer.
Or something like this?
'I want to change the world!'
What, this, something like this?
I don't like such grand things
I'm not sure
I'm more than just a number
dealing with people
Helping people in need
I want to do it
Hahahahaha!
Hey! Park Byun, I am like this
Are you such a great person?
I didn't realize it, huh? Hey
Okay, I understand everything.
Let me be honest.
What's the real reason?
uh?
Just for no other reason
If possible
If you want to live while doing good things
Are you a strange person?
Why does everyone not believe and doubt?
Why does good faith have to be proven?
Is selfishness assumed?
Ha…
Yes, Park Gippeum
Let's not be discouraged
Just go home
Eat something delicious first
Fighting
"Joie de viva
“Bakery Cafe”
Hello everyone!
- uh…
- came?
Hello, Attorney Jang.
Huh?
Is this a mushroom too?
Huh, pretty
Maybe this
Attorney Jang
Did you put it there?
Ah, those are egg mushrooms.
This is a child raised in a greenhouse.
It grows well outside too.
very sturdy
Attorney Jang
Fighting
Well, I have to go to the data room...
fish oil, baby
Ah…
- Uh
- Wow
Wow, this keeps happening...
thank you, yes
‘Due to violation of the doctor’s obligation to explain’…
'For varicose veins and deformities of the lower extremities
'Those who underwent surgery'
Hmm
Welcome
hello
Isn’t Jung So-min there?
Ah, ah, later…
Just a moment
Please tell me a little more...
You're not just going, are you?
Somin, if that’s true.
There is a possibility
Ugh~
Ouch!
why?
At the last meeting
It's over.
No, to God
Are you going to send me a copy of the complaint?
So where is the address?
101 Dogok-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul
Hey, do you live in Gangnam?
What about God for new mothers?
uh?
101 Dogok-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul
Woongsan General Hospital, affiliated with Woongsan Group
I go there
I will send you a complaint for damages.
Kang Hoon~
Ah…
You came early?
Didn’t you go to work?
Ugh, mommy hurts.
My back hurts too
Is it a cold or my throat hurts?
You decided not to eat it.
alcohol
I ate because I was sick, because I was sick!
Okay
Ha…
Why is life like this?
I'm going to get punished
Living carelessly
Just alive
Then
Am I my mother’s punishment?
what?
But I
What are you being punished for?
Jeong So-min
I got pregnant with Kang Hoon
It was a time when I was living in a runaway family.
Woongsan Welfare Foundation made the connection.
At Woongsan Hospital
They say I received treatment.
In fact, Somin
from the beginning
I didn't want to give birth
It was an unwanted pregnancy
Because I was too young to handle it.
However, this hospital
Somin’s intention
How many times have you ignored it?
Towards giving birth again and again
I did judo.
Huh? Why on earth do you do that?
That's right
Moreover, this hospital
I guess there was no reason to be careless.
In a family where the mother ran away from home
Every day, I eat snacks in Gangsoju.
I'm eating a meal
Even though I clearly know
One proper inspection
It seems like it wasn't implemented.
Ha, I heard it was a conglomerate-affiliated hospital.
Well, were you busy treating VIPs?
The cause of Kang Hoon’s lower limb paralysis is
prenatal
caused by immature brain development
It's deformed
Oh, I'm not sure about this either.
Maternal alcoholism and malnutrition
It might have had an impact.
Right on time
Even if only an ultrasound examination was performed
Checking for brain abnormalities in the fetus
It was possible
Right, Attorney Kang?
huh?
Then Lawyer Kang is already…
in the data room
Medical litigation materials related to lower extremity paralysis
What I took
This is Attorney Kang, right?
Isn't it?
Oh, yeah, whatever.
That's right, that's right
But as much as Park Byeon
I couldn't make progress
Wow, that’s amazing, Attorney Park.
Because I got good grades
Because he came from the No. 1 law firm.
Huh!
If it is Woongsan Hospital
to the union there
I know someone
Let's take a look at the internal situation.
Fighting
If it is Woongsan Group
The opponent will be Woo Myung-hoon again.
Yes?
- why?
- He's the consulting attorney there.
Not only there
Most conglomerates
Hey~
You are a truly talented person.
Wow, I really want to learn
No, hmm!
So, it's not like that.
- I…
- What isn't it?
Your eyes are so, so scary now
Everyone please stand up
Everyone please sit down
Me, your honor.
I'm sorry, but
Before the trial begins...
You mean you applied for reallocation?
It's just as you expected.
Yeah
Kang Hoon’s case
It was allocated to Civil Affairs 7 alone.
Did it go well?
Then~
7It was Judge Kim Jin-oh who was the sole judge.
He is severely visually impaired.
Huh, really?
Wow, what a great person.
I don't know
Is that necessarily a good thing?
yes?
Isn't that good?
No, I guess
About the lives of disabled people
You probably know better than anyone else.
Well, please sympathize with me.
Wouldn't it be so?
Isn’t that right, Attorney Kang?
You know Judge Kim well, right?
Oh no
I don't know
Except for being a blind judge.
Ah, Attorney Kang.
Are there some judges you don't know?
After all, only successful judges
You know it well.
Wow, this chair is
It’s very uncomfortable, especially!
By the way, the defendant
I guess I'll give it a try.
Something like an application for reallocation
yes
I'm sorry, but
I guess it's a medical lawsuit.
The amount of reference books and evidence
It can be massive...
'The blind judge
'How can you read it?'
Are you worried?
no, what
I don't necessarily mean that.
The material in Braille is probably mine.
You'll read it faster than your lawyer.
Materials that do not
small intestine
Plaintiff Kim Kang-hoon, defendant…
When a screen reader reads
listen
original
Isn’t a trial all about hearing?
I'll listen to it all even if I stay up all night
You can submit any material you want.
Oh my, how dare I
The judge's work ability
Would you doubt it?
Just…
Just?
Because the content of the case is the content
If this court proceeds,
I wonder if there is some misunderstanding.
Well, there are concerns like that...
defendant agent
yes
I am not a disabled judge
I'm just a judge
This trial too
No different from any other trial
We will proceed
Application for reallocation is rejected.
But to us
There won't be any advantage
Ha…
Is that so?
When going through immigration at a foreign airport
- Where do you usually stand?
- It's me, what?
If only he could look this kind.
To the young female examiner...
Ding
It's most likely to be late
Why? Why is that so?
The more you belong to a minority within a group, the more
It is better to work according to principles.
Because there are many
Because I don't want to be misunderstood
Ah…
Why are you misunderstood?
This lawsuit
On groundless speculation
It is based on
The plaintiff side
They are only raising vague suspicions.
objective evidence
Unable to present
The defendant's hospital
It is the best hospital in the country
Tests normally required for pregnant women
There's no way it wouldn't have been implemented
Just to prove that point
All medical records at the time
Please submit it
I applied for an order to submit documents, but
Defendant is not responding
It's been over 10 years
Document retention period has expired
These materials have already been discarded.
The defendant hospital
Materials that are past their retention period
informally
Are you not preserving it?
For medical research?
Oh, I don't know.
Where did you say that?
I don't know if you heard
We don't know
- Your honor!
- Yes
Items that have passed the legal retention period
I think that's right
That the record currently exists
Unless there is objective evidence
Prove it another way
fact
The defendant hospital
I'm very embarrassed
From the beginning, I was in a situation where I had nowhere to go.
Plaintiff's mother
The best hospital in the country
at the defendant's hospital
Starting with being able to give birth
Wanting to help runaway teenagers
It was thanks to the goodwill of the Woongsan Welfare Foundation.
True
The word ingratitude
There's no way I can't think of it...
defendant agent
It has nothing to do with the trial, stop.
Yes, I understand, your honor.
Just
We early
I would like you to conclude the lawsuit.
What the Plaintiff Can Do
Because it doesn't seem like much.
That's it.
Your honor
We are with the Health Insurance Committee.
Fact inquiry
I will apply
What is it about?
Defendant Woongsan Hospital
Implemented over the past 10 years
Number of abortion surgeries performed
and other
Large hospitals of similar size
Number of implementations
What is the purpose of proof?
The defendant hospital
I don't know what the intention is
deliberately
Avoiding abortion surgery
The point is that childbirth has been induced.
Lawyer Kang
Lawyer Kang!
What do you mean by that all of a sudden?
Did you find any evidence?
No, there is no evidence or anything.
No, there is no evidence
Such a bombshell statement...
Earlier, Woo Myung-hoon
Is there something you said?
What about ingratitude…
uh?
Ah, ‘Woongsan Welfare Foundation’
'At the defendant's hospital
‘He allowed me to receive medical treatment.’
‘To help runaway teenagers’?
While listening to that
I thought about it again
In fact, Somin
from the beginning
I didn't want to give birth
It was an unwanted pregnancy
Because I was too young to handle it.
However, this hospital
Somin’s intention
How many times have you ignored it?
Towards giving birth again and again
I did judo.
Why bother?
pregnant runaway teenagers
Was it connected to Woongsan Hospital?
Well, properly
It's not like I care
It may be a ridiculous idea, but
Maybe this is all
If there is any intention...
Pregnancy abortion rate
one of the highest groups
He must be a runaway teenager.
Like Jeong So-min
Ha…
Through people in the Woongsan Hospital union
I heard it
Indeed, the life of the mother
Until it becomes dangerous
abortion surgery
They say they didn't do it
Because of that, among young doctors
They said there were a lot of complaints.
The risk of missing the timing is too high
I'm nervous
Ha, about the condition of the fetus.
Properly to the mother
There's no way I can explain it.
Hmm…
uh?
At the Health Insurance Committee
Actually, did you get an answer to the inquiry you made?
What do you say?
and…
I declined to reply.
Hospital trade secrets
It's a matter
These are really...
Perfect for me, eh
yes
Make a phone call to the office on the right.
I received what you sent
Thank you
Chairman, that person
Woo Myung-hoon
When I was in the Chief Civil Affairs Office of the Blue House.
This is the person who landed with a parachute.
yes
But you guys
It comes out like this, right?
Ha, no, what should I do?
Korean civil servants
How to be most scared
I have to write it.
What is it?
Me, Chairman.
When sleeping in a massage chair
Don't wake me up
Oh, hey, Chairman!
why?
sorry
I told you to wait outside
Suddenly, recklessly...
what?
Who are you?
Oh, are you awake?
Hey, nice to meet you
My name is lawyer David Kang.
David?
Are you from Israel?
Oh, but Chairman
Hey, this
Is the putter okay? Is this gold?
Don't hit rock bottom! Tsk
Umm
I'm sorry
Ah~
In fact, I sent an inquiry
If you came here to throw a tantrum
Get out right away
Because I have already stated my position
You're coming in droves
Hey, how old am I?
What am I doing, throwing a tantrum, what?
I'm not that kind of person
Oh my
Did it fall off?
This is a complaint to be filed in court.
Against the Chairman
What?
‘Information disclosure request’?
Just whatever, it's no big deal
It's just the chairman's office expenses, whatever.
Corporate card usage history
Oh my
I usually pay for my wife’s perm.
You're using it as a corporate card, huh?
You're great, you're homely.
I need to learn this stuff, so sweet
- Attorney Kang?
- huh?
Every successful negotiation on earth is
Sit and talk calmly
It has come true
Come on, let’s sit down, come on.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes
Let's sit down and talk.
Now again...
‘Purchase details of furniture and equipment for the director’s office’
No, the place you were sleeping earlier.
Over there, over there
That's a limited edition edition.
Where did you buy that?
Ah, this is
I went on a business trip overseas and paid it with my own money…
overseas business trip
‘Overseas business trip expenses usage details’
Are you researching the cutting-edge medical industry?
Well, where did you go on your overseas business trip?
her…
Oh, that's right
I'm going to have a Maldives drink in mojito.
As expected
High-tech medical care is in the Maldives!
Huh? But
The person who went with me
You're not my wife?
Lawyer Kang!
Ah, oh, oh, oh
Chairman, my goodness.
- Chairman
- Lawyer
Sir, no, doctor.
No, what's important about the title?
Oh, it's you, you
Hey David!
Slowly, slowly in conversation
Let's solve it through conversation.
Then have some tea
Shall we talk about it slowly?
yes
suddenly
Actually, I received a reply to my inquiry?
Obviously last time
I said it was difficult to answer
Ah…
me too…
Uh, what happened?
I don't know either
Uh, well, anyway
The issues in this case and
Not directly related
It's visible...
91%
According to the results of this reply
Woongsan General Hospital
The pregnancy abortion rate is
Compared to the average of other hospitals
91% less
Attorney Woo, this is
Is it a coincidence? Or
- Is it a miracle?
- No, that…
Well, what are you proving?
Numbers are just numbers
Each mother’s situation is different.
It’s natural to have different thoughts…
I know you will
very interesting information
I will submit additional information.
Your honor
Korean anti-abortion movement groups
biggest sponsor
Do you know who it is?
Your Honor, the plaintiff's attorney
With claims that have nothing to do with the issue
delaying the trial
There's a lot involved.
Attorney Woo
of these organizations
5 years worth of accounting audit data
in our office
A stubborn fan of Muddepo...
Fish oil!
Park Byun?
- ah…
- Good morning
What, what, what…
I've been here all weekend
Why aren't you going home?
Look at this
What is this?
Hey, how did you find all this?
How do you do it?
I just found everything with Mudepo.
Heh…
a lawyer
According to the results of one-by-one analysis,
The biggest sponsor!
in hong kong
It's a foundation called Elliott.
In Korea
It's a completely unknown place.
Hey, what does that mean?
The address of the Elliott Foundation is
Although it is in Hong Kong
Even in Korea
There is a place to deliver mail.
That address!
Dogok-ro, Gangnam-gu, Seoul
Wait a minute
- There…
- Yes
That's right
Defendant Woongsan General Hospital
And in the same building
This is the address of Woongsan Welfare Foundation.
And Elliot
Died at age 30
Chairman Choi Woong-san’s only son
This is Woojin Choi’s American name.
Chairman Choi Woong-san
After Choi Woo-jin's death
sudden religious activity
I started to concentrate
After that, Chairman Choi
In our country
The most fundamentalist denomination
The biggest sponsor
He also became an elder
It's a guess
Even if Chairman Choi
some strong religious beliefs
Even if there was
Directly to hospital staff
Evidence that specific instructions were given
Nowhere else...
That's power
Even without direct instructions
tissue physiology
The will of the top is
It has no choice but to be implemented
According to the organization's implicit policy
Medical staff who do not comply
Being disadvantaged for all kinds of reasons
I had to leave the hospital
relevant evidence
I will submit it soon
yes please
Okay, this is enough.
Seems like a lot to do, right?
defendant agent
Well… relevant evidence
Please be sure to submit
Uh, okay.
- Mr.
- Huh?
You have skills, really?
Hey, man
You know it's an honor, huh?
Even though I’m like this…
thank you
And I'm sorry
You had a hard time because I forced you to do it, right?
What, suddenly?
Can't you get used to it? Why is this happening?
I don't have money to pay the fee.
I have to do something like this
I thought so
I wondered what was going on, hey, ayu
But
Mom never comes, ever?
Just stamp the power of attorney.
Doing useless things
What a mess it was
people like us
How can they win against such a big hospital?
Can you really win?
hmm
medical records
In the end, I couldn't secure it.
I can only prove half of it.
Is that so?
Then
Am I my mother’s punishment?
what?
But I
What are you being punished for?
submitted to this court
Considering all the evidence
Plaintiff's disability
When I was in the womb
Diagnosis was already possible
being judged
If so, the defendant hospital
Diagnosis and explanation obligations related to this
It was not implemented properly
I see it
But
The defendant hospital gave the plaintiff's mother
Precautions during pregnancy
that it was not properly notified and
That is the plaintiff's disability
The fact that it caused
There is evidence to admit this
It's not enough
Therefore, for the occurrence of failure
Claim for damages
I can't admit it
Ha, as expected…
What's left is
The defendant hospital
Plaintiff's possible disability
Diagnosis and explanation duties
Whether intentionally or negligently
The point is that it was not implemented.
To put it simply,
opportunity to abort the plaintiff
It means they didn't give it to you.
As a result, the defendant's
To acknowledge the obligation to pay damages
we are very
You have to answer difficult questions
In order for the plaintiff to win this case,
‘Kang Hoon, a twelve-year-old boy,
'Better than anything in this world'
'Something that wasn't born at all
'I'm healed'
'His life'
‘Life itself is nothing but a loss’
Oh my
a miserable conclusion
It has to come down
As an individual, I too
What are the minds of the plaintiffs?
Did it come all the way to this court?
a little bit
you can guess
But I
Not as an individual, but as a judge.
I'm standing here
And the Constitution of the Republic of Korea
Anyone with a disability
Even if there is no one
rich or poor
everyone's life
that they are equally dignified
As the most fundamental premise
I am using it
constitutionally
Unless there is a right more precious than life.
The state of being lifeless
The hypothetical judgment that it is better than life is
It's impossible
What life is worth existing?
what kind of life
Rather
Would it be better if it never existed?
This judgment
For humans
It belongs to the realm of the impossible
Therefore
Plaintiff Kim Kang-hoon’s birth
Because it cannot be recognized as damage
Plaintiff's claim is
There's no reason
I dismiss this
made my heart beat
Those beautiful languages
This time
It felt like a huge wall
Ah…
Ultimately, the existing Supreme Court precedent
I can't turn it over
All relevant foreign precedents were also submitted.
No, it's not Woongsan's fault.
It's not going away.
It's not like I'm responsible
You make me give birth unconditionally and you don’t know me.
Does this make sense?
Why do you do this to me
legally
It can't be helped, right?
Ah, the logic is flawless.
no
I'm all for that
I think it's beautiful bullshit.
What is it? Everyone?
No way
Have you ever thought about giving up like this?
If you don't understand
Please memorize it.
We will definitely win
If it's a losing fight
It hasn't even started!
Do you understand!
I believe you, Attorney Kang!
Wow, do you even bow down?
What kind of pseudo-religion is this?
Then eat some snacks first.
Shall we have a meeting?
Appeal Strategy
Oh, if you're hungry
My head doesn't work well.
- Please sit down.
- Hmm, good.
Kid!
With this cookie fluttering
Will sugar supplementation work?
Well, today
especially in the world
The most delicious bakery
I'm shooting
Let's go!
- oh! yes
- You…
Hey, you said you lived?
- Okay, let's eat and cheer up!
- Let's go, lawyer.
Eat and cheer up, sister!
It seems like you lost in a strange way?
Huh, French?
'Joie de viva'
joy of life
No way!
- uh?
- There's a power outage!
Oh my, oh my
Is it your sister's birthday?
kid…
With the meaning of let’s all fight together
I prepared it once.
Wow! There are so many fruits
There are too many
Now, now, everyone.
When I say ‘pro bono’
You say ‘victory’
I'll blow out the candles
Pro bono!
Victory!
Huh~
Victory is unsophisticated…
huh?
- Where have you seen that guy before?
- Now
Where did you see it?
Huh, ah, taxi
Let me introduce you
It's my mom and dad
hello
These are lawyers who work with me.
names in order
Lawyers Jang, Young, and Sil
- Hello
- If you report
to find the owner
Announcements are made for more than a week
Ah
I want to tie that guy's hands.
If he doesn't move his hands
Can't you speak?
river, da, upper
- Ha…
- Lawyer
hello
Attorneys Hwang, Jun, and Woo
Hello!
Lawyers Yoo, Nan, and Hee
hello
‘Enjoy your meal’
Thank you, I will enjoy it.
Just a little bit
-Thank you!
- thank you
I'll eat well!
sit down, sit down
Enjoy
no
Do you know how to sign?
slightly
Sister!
Such a cool bakery
Was it your daughter?
I hope so. This is Bbangsuni’s dream.
Huh! yes?
In my real past life
I would have saved something, really.
That's right~
I'll eat well!
So delicious
- Park Byeon
- Huh?
that…
It looks like it opened not long ago?
Oh, after all
Do you have a good sense of vision?
It's only been a month now
So what about before that?
Ah, in the past
I used to have a bigger store than this.
When I was in high school, my dad
Stop being deceived by bad friends
I completely ruined the store.
Like that
For the crime of even offering a guarantee
Taking on bank debt
My dad used to bake bread with my mom
Driving a taxi for over 10 years
I barely made a living
In a home without any shortages
You said you grew up loved, right?
What about those people?
I don't know what real hardship is.
Ah, hmm!
Still, this talented daughter
I added the money I earned through hard work as a lawyer.
I even took out a small loan.
This store just opened, right?
That’s cool, Attorney Park.
Why are you embarrassed again?
It's true
It's cool
Mmm!
Do you like apricots? Don’t you buy apricots?
I'm more than just sweet
I like this
sour and bitter
It's just like life
- Yes
- I'll try it.
- Mmm!
- Um
It's so cool!
eww!
I don't use coffee, it's delicious
Eat a lot
But Judge Guk Gook-jun
Doesn’t that seem a bit strict?
don't worry
Lawyer Kang
I'm sure you have a plan for the appeal.
Plaintiff's representative?
yes
This, what
In the appeal trial
Is this a case where there is more to do?
In the first trial
There's enough to do
I think you've done it all?
In response to the wise first trial ruling
Without giving in
To the plaintiff's attorney who even appealed
I would like to ask
What on earth did the defendant do wrong?
I value life more than anything else
Is it wrong?
No way, I was born disabled
It's better not to be born
Are you thinking?
If not
Plaintiff's appeal is
In fact, there is no benefit
This is the defendant's position.
Your honor
Defendant Woongsan Hospital
that all life is dignified
Woongsan Group Chairman Choi Woong-san
according to sacred beliefs
Doctor of a pregnant woman 16 years younger than me
Ignoring it
Plaintiff Kim Kang-hoon
I made you born into this world
The first trial ruling was also
All life is dignified and equal
for holy reasons
Life is whatever life is.
They say it can't be any harm
The plaintiff's claim was dismissed.
You are great
I was impressed too
Therefore, in this appeal
Really, Woongsan Group
And this Republic of Korea
All life is dignified and equal
Are you being treated?
one by one
I would like to consider it
Just stay still
Just in words
When you say ‘dignity’ and ‘equality’
Are we becoming dignified and equal?
No, the judge
Is it okay to lie?
The court said to the child
Is it okay to cheat?
Plaintiff's representative!
What are you doing now, yeah?
Is the trial some kind of joke?
No, I'm just asking.
All life is dignified and equal
The Constitution of the Republic of Korea
Is it a scam or not?
I…
Wait a minute
no, work
Why are you raising it like this?
If this boy sitting here, Kang Hoon,
In this society so far
Treated with dignity and equality
If I couldn't survive
The saying that all life has dignity
It's just beautiful bullshit
If it turns out!
I am
With your own wrong beliefs
Plaintiff Kim Kang-hoon
In this world as I please
The very thing that made me born
that person
This is crazy...
Your honor
Woongsan Group
To sue Chairman Choi Woong-san
I'll take you to court.
Your honor, this is
Do you think it makes sense?
Uh, what a ridiculous claim…
It's the beginning again, making that work bigger.
Fish oil, that tube type
ha
I really want to learn, really
- What do you learn?
- Ugh!
Chairman
I have something urgent to report to you.
It's no different...
what about now
What are you doing?
Oh, the judge
Go directly to the scene
Getting emotional by watching and listening
Isn’t this on-site verification?
It was like that when I was a judge.
in press play
Please stop using Kang Hoon.
Fighting for yourself
Probably not, right?
I'm going to build a winning team
If you don't like it, leave
Against Chairman Choi Woong-san
Separate damages lawsuit
I will raise it
The one who gave birth to Kang Hoon
Do you think it's a loss?
If Kang Hoon’s life is a loss
Who caused the damage?
Is it perhaps because of money?
of others
involved in life and death
What other permissions are there?
Do you have any?
please tell me
What effort should I make?
Will I be able to live like other children?
To O&Partners
A being that is harmful?
I don't plan on leaving it behind
Pro bono team
My brother too
debtor
Mr. Park Chang-soon
order
Wingardium leviosa
debtor
Indemnify
Huh? uh? Mom, Mom…
Reasons for disallowance of exemption
Because there are no relevant facts
We decide like this
Applicant's remaining
Jointly guaranteed debt is now
completely
It's gone
The order the judge memorized at that moment was
Appearing in ‘Harry Potter’
More than all those orders
It was an even cooler magic spell.
Now, next time in 2015
686…
Oh, so you’re hearing impaired? that…
Is this right?
Congratulations
You won
I guess that's right